{
    "id": "e26dcc70302a4269977a45048b843d96",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Run Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Can you get some sugar from the shop? We have run ………………",
            "description": "To run out of something is to have none of it left.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "101ff7f1a42941b5b1d08a439d0db97c"
        },
        {
            "question": "This car runs ……………… petrol.",
            "description": "When a car runs on petrol, it is powered by petrol.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "58e9b232754f4da2a82cc1849f36cc58"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ran …………….. from home because he had no one to love him there.",
            "description": "To run away is to escape or to run from somebody who is chasing you.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3b9777de6bbd43cb82567f23d527b1fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cancer runs ……………. his family. Both his parents died of it.",
            "description": "If a disease runs in a family, it is kind of hereditary. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f5a3ee232cf0405d91d944535c75b81d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police constable ran ………………. the thief but he could not catch him.",
            "description": "To run after somebody is to chase them. ",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "out",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6dad400494344f58947941cdc8123d20"
        },
        {
            "question": "When we were kids we would spend the entire afternoon running ……………. the neighborhood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "around",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "817fe1cb6d8b4f839fda41f85d3c6785"
        },
        {
            "question": "I want to run ……………… President.",
            "description": "To run for President is to try to be elected President.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7f9121ecfb54277a8d357ad87c6e024"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ran …………….. an old friend of mine yesterday.",
            "description": "To run into somebody is to meet them unexpectedly.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "into",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a4f8a008ee2341c389c43499c1ce4d8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you run ………………. hundred copies of this document?",
            "description": "Run off can mean make photocopies.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "off",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4362928819244d34aa507bc7a004a560"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ran ………………. a dog while driving home from work.",
            "description": "To run over a dog is to hit it with a vehicle.",
            "answers": [
                "after",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ef515ec385d44cea3bcadcaf63b0fc8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has run ……………… a huge debt on his credit cards.",
            "description": "To run up debt is to spend a lot of money on credit.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ca455f715cd4586a0c39b106606619a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran ………………. the presentation one more time to ensure that everything is perfect.",
            "description": "To run through a presentation is to practice it quickly.",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "over",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c363c8e7e0cb4cd5813a2e0b5f96076d"
        }
    ]
}